[{"answer": "Obviously, it's been a tragedy from the beginning for me.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "What is your reaction to what has happened here with your longtime friend James DiMaggio?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "That's correct, yes.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "You, Berry and James DiMaggio have gone on regular camping trips together, is that correct?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What kind of man is he?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "You know, there is always a possibility of something.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Do you think there is credence to that family?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, yes.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Just to clarify -- just to clarify, you mean Hannah, not Megan?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "PANSWICK: You know, if anything, his life, I believe, was getting simpler.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Any upheaval with a partner or with a business or anything?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "She really believes that she's not getting a fair shake and that Jim especially isn't getting a share shake, that, you know, everybody is very upset and it's tragic what's happened.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What is her state of mind?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Not that I know of.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Was he seeing anybody currently that you are aware of?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Berry -- Smokey is not really -- I mean, I think Smokey is probably twice, probably once at Berry's wedding and maybe one other time.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Right, and Berry, obviously, again, Smokey Robinson's son, do you know if Smokey is aware of this connection and what has happened?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "You know, there is a couple things that I find interesting.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Was he somebody that had any kind of military training or training with explosives or access to this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "I would say beyond that.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "There was no problem there?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, if that were the case -- I mean, I don't necessarily know if that's the case.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "What would you say to him?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, he's certainly hoping it isn't his friend and we live in such a litigious society, Piers, that probably you and I both should say that this man is accused of kidnapping this girl and murdering her mother and probably her brother.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "ICH: No, and they do it all the time.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Is there anything inherently wrong anyway in networks running documentaries or drama series on big political figures of the time?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I have no idea whether she'll run or not.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Do you think that she can win, or has her time come and gone?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "What if it was Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Do you think he can actually win the general election?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "But look, this is a serious job.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Is there a chance?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, that's --", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Is he the most shameless politician in American history?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Does it really matter the forum he chooses?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "You know, is there a -- is there an opportunity there for people to make a stand, perhaps even consider a boycott and say no, you're not going to behave in this Dickensian (ph) way?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "In limbo and at least we're out of that hotel.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "And in terms of Edward Snowden, what -- what is your overview where we are with him?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "You know, it is a farce.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What is served here this (ph) fast (ph) and particularly, if he's about to start grilling some of his victims?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm doing great, Piers.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "What I'm -- what I'm signaling is that I -- yes, I think it's a very important time in our country's history and particularly, and as I talked about here tonight within the Republican Party, and you know, we see a lot of debate and division there.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Are you basically signaling that you're back in the race again?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Yes, we did.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "You must know Iowa pretty well because I think from memory, you went to them like 350 different parts of it, didn't you, in the last Republican Nominee race?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Yes, I -- I think it is.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "The gap between the rich and poor in America, is it -- is it still the economy driving most people's concern?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, I guess the whole point is, you know, what makes Hillary Clinton such a unique individual that she would be treated barely differently than any other politician I can think of.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Can we expect to see you and Reince Priebus bouncing back on the airwave saying what a great idea it was after all?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know how comfortable I'd be on (ph).", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Are you comfortable with that one?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I -- I announced some exciting news -- personal news that we're actually doing a small audition to our -- our house because we have to put an elevator in and handicapped bathroom and bedroom because Bella is going strong and doing great.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "How is she doing?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Well, just like you said, I was spear-fishing.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Tell me what happened?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "You know, I'll -- I'll tell you, to be honest with you, I believe with all my heart that God sustained me in that moment of time to give me no fear and no worry, no anxiety.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Did you think that you -- you had it -- it was like, kill or you how were you feeling at that moment?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What is it with you and monkeys?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I think that he's -- he's continually challenging me to trust him, which is what I believe that we all need to do through hard times, through good times, through bad times.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Or is he picking you out for special attention?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, one time was kind of my fault actually.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Why do you think monkeys dislike him so much?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "More or less.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Is that -- is that what I'm hearing?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "It's still a lot to take in.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "How are you feeling about it all?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Are you going to be back to normal?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "I mean, if the good lord is watching tonight, and I'm sure he is, would you like him just to lay off you a bit for a while?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "No, I don't play the lottery.", "docId": "130808pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "And playing the lottery?", "qSentId": 566}]